A model student in the eyes of adults
They all look the same
And in their opinion…
Model students do not have "sexual desire"
But in the Joseon era
A man has no heirs when he reaches 16 years old
It will make a mess
Obviously there is already a royal concubine
The royal family still has to choose a concubine and a concubine for the crown prince
what does this mean
Convert to modern age
People probably had sexual experience since they were young
Even became a parent
Your Highness
Although people's life span has become longer
But this does not mean
The physiological needs of puberty are delayed
Boys masturbating
generally accepted by society
But girls
Especially model students
What would the adults think?
Even a castrated eunuch has a sexual desire
and sexual curiosity
They think we don't
It was then that Xiaojing began to realize
I am a precocious child
It's like she's possessed by a pervert
Feel everything around you
are full of erotic hints
Xiaojing who can't suppress her curiosity
Finally stepped through that door
However…
What greeted her was unexpected difficulties
The name of my primary school
mother's name
What idiot designed these problems?
Just find out the profile
Questions that anyone can answer
Favorite anime character
Do you want to prove that you are a otaku?
The place of first kiss
How rude
What about people who have never kissed?
The name of the classmate next door in elementary school
Six years of primary school
Change seats once a semester
The classmates next door changed at least 12 times
Whose name do you want me to write?
[Elementary School Mathematics]
If you don’t work hard on the questions, your grades will get better.
You should focus on reading the textbooks
[Lin Xianzhi ranks first in the school
Excluded transfer students]
This is what the art cram school teacher helped you draw, right?
The brushstrokes are completely different
Too obvious
I'm not making up the art.
Really?
Then you'd better go and make up for it.
Hello
The fight started
Should I persuade you to have a fight?
Everyone
It's a pity that Hyun Ji is going to study in the UK.
We have been together for so long, so we should have feelings for each other.
Hyun Ji before leaving
Do you want to say something to your classmates?
I heard that the British like number one very much
She went bankrupt because of her father's company
Study in the UK to avoid debt
But even so, she is still very proud
Xiaojing thought that the "annoying number one" finally left
The first place is finally hers
But…
Life never goes as we expect
Jai Yi is not only beautiful, but also has good grades
Xiaojing
And it's very popular
Name Liu Jieyi
Will serve as the second semester of 2018
Student Union President
For Xiaojing, Jie Yi is the opponent
More annoying than Xianzhi
But she can't show it
Because…
I Liu Jieyi
will work together with Vice President Cui Jing
Complete the student union work for this semester
At that time they were still the best partners
Xiaojing, are you free after school?
Do you want to go eat spicy fried rice cake together?
[Zheng Hazhen’s ranking is unknown
Sera Elementary School grass]
-That...
-I have something to ask you
-I'm telling you...
You say it first
It doesn't matter. Just say it first.
Actually nothing
Can you give me Jay's phone number?
Actually I kind of like her...
The word "vice" that I can't get rid of
She is taller among girls
Just my type...
Because you know Jai very well
We are friends. Do me this favor.
please
Leave it to you
adverb side effect side hustle subtitle
Vice president, deputy squad leader, vice president...
It seems that the word "vice"
Will never disappear from Xiaojing
This makes Xiaojing extremely sad
Because that means she always loses.
It can always only be second place
[Join]
[adult.com]
["Good-natured Competition"]
[Album]
[Selected by University Entrance Examination Question Setters]
By the way, Seulgi, why did you transfer here?
Actually I know you were in the previous school
Ranked first in the school in every exam
You really know everything about me
[Searching for missing children Yu Seulqi]
It seems that you also liked to play princess when you were a child.
I didn't expect you to have that kind of past
Thank you for telling me this
[Choose 1]
[Case content]
[Because the patient was unable to breathe on his own when he arrived at the hospital,
Endotracheal intubation was performed immediately]
[Endotracheal intubation]
[cyanosis]
[peritonitis]
[Sepsis]
[Medical Negligence]
[Doctor kills]
[Hospital director kills mistress
Arrested by the police for murder]
It will be more comfortable for you to wear this
thank you
Auntie, Jay's menu will change starting tomorrow.
Have you confirmed it?
Yes
Be sure to pay attention to protein
to carbohydrate ratio
There are also medicines that should be taken first on an empty stomach
Start with B12
ok dean
Why didn't your friend come down with you?
She hasn't had breakfast yet, right?
It wasn't her father who drove her away, right?
How could I drive away this distinguished guest?
It has been waiting for sister
Why doesn't sister come back?
It's embarrassing enough to fail the college entrance exam.
I have to take the exam again in the same year as my sister.
Do you think she can concentrate on studying at home?
You should understand her
Did my sister say it herself?
Said she didn't want to go home
Yes
Is that why I didn’t call you back even once?
I miss her this time...
I've really made up my mind
Please help me tell Liu Jiena
No matter how hard she tries, she can never surpass me
Zhu Yili
Why are you wearing sneakers today?
Still walking to school
You are so smart, I decided to listen to you
Walking seems to be the best exercise
Yes
You are right to listen to me
But your complexion seems to have improved
I thought it was the sequelae of the squad leader election
will last a week
Because I found something that can heal myself
Powerful vitamins
Jin Nali
It seems that's true
The "new stones" crowd out the "old stones"
what
Hey, I heard that Jin Nali is going to transfer schools.
She is in the teacher's office with her mother now
true or false
why
Yu Seqi
wait for me
You clearly saw me just now
Why didn't you even say hello?
where are you going
Go to the teacher's office
why
Go get the roster
Oh
Why did you go back by yourself yesterday?
My mother told me to go home
I almost misunderstood
what do you think it is
I thought you didn't want to go to school with me
Just ran home
not like that
-Why did Nali suddenly change schools?
-It shouldn’t be easy to make such a decision...
Don't know
Do you want to say goodbye to her and wish her a safe journey?
do you want to go
Nali
Oh
I heard you're going to transfer schools
It’s just a shame that we have just matured
I think too
Bon voyage
If you want to get into a good university
You'd better use social media less
Do you know
Liu Jieyi
Cui Jing
Kim Bum Soo
Copy content directly from the Internet
Do you remember this during the interview?
Zhao Yaluo
The interview scores at Yanrui University have worsened
It's impossible to pass the exam if your autobiography is so boring.
Neither wrote about specialties other than academics
There's nothing touching about it either
What on earth should you do?
There is only one autobiography that makes people’s eyes light up
Whose is it
The monitor of your class
Teacher, why don’t we read Seulgi’s autobiography?
She writes creatively
Future plans and motivations are also well written.
It’s really worth learning
I also want you to take a look
But after all, the autobiography is about personal privacy.
Just forget it
Everyone
Go back and think about your own story
Or ask your college counselor for help.
No need to salute
what on earth did you write
Let the Chinese teacher praise me greatly
What? Even I can’t watch it?
Nothing special
Jay
How many points did you get
why do you want to know
Because if I'm not the only one who didn't get an A+
I should feel better
Should we ask Seulgi to teach everyone a lesson?
If she wants to help us with lessons, I want to hear it too
I also want to...
Seulgi, you'd better hide your autobiography
Go and have a meal
How
Are you also dissatisfied with your scores?
No way
Of course I have to humbly accept the score given by the teacher.
So what's the matter with you?
I want to ask the class teacher for leave
I’m going back to piano lessons today
She seems to have gone to eat
Then I'll wait for her here
By the way, teacher
The hairstyle you changed this time suits you very well
Yeli, your autobiography is quite insincere.
The result is usually the same.
Teacher, how can I be insincere?
I just like to gossip
Teacher Li
Do you want to go to dinner?
good
You still have the nerve to say it?
[Autobiography of Yu Seqi]
[Caihua Girls' High School]
seulgi what's wrong
What's going on
What's wrong with you
what are you looking for
My…
Autobiography is missing
stop
Start over
Stop…
I can't listen anymore
I'm leaving first
what
You have no intention of going to college playing the harp, do you?
Not like that
open palms
The harp player doesn’t even have blisters on his hands.
Thin skin and tender meat
your hands
Only suitable for manicure
Full of jewelry
Don’t look for me again in the future
Professor I'm sorry
I will really work hard
If I don't get into college, I'm dead
Afraid of death…
Then you and your parents should work hard
Before buying you a designer bag
You should pay the tuition fees first
what
Go back and tell your family
I must make up the outstanding tuition fees this week.
you know this bag
What is the current second-hand price?
Take it first
You can pay me back when I send you the tuition next week
For your pity sake, I will keep it safe for you first.
i know
thank you
Damn that's why
Everyone must have a brand-name bag
[Yu Seqi]
Jay
This is really a misunderstanding. I...
Lost children nursery
Mathematics teacher acute sepsis
medical school autopsy
No one is allowed to look at it
without my permission
No one is allowed to read her autobiography
Did you hear that?
Jay
let's talk
I…
Will definitely find out
Who took your autobiography?
And spread it without permission
why
why did you do that
Do you still need to ask?
Aren't you angry?
Of course I'm angry
But I don’t seem as angry as you
What are you angry about?
Because it's your business...
you answer the phone
[Princess]
My unfortunate past was originally only known to you
Now everyone knows
Is that why you are unhappy?
[Searching for missing children]
You already knew that
I grew up in a kindergarten
Also, my dad passed away not long ago.
Teacher Yu Daohe
Who is it really?
what to do
Accidentally used too much force
Originally I just wanted to pull out one
I received a tip
Want to confirm
So I want to help you do a hair test
what are you talking about
Nali
I heard you are addicted to drugs
Jay
Send this to our hospital
You can immediately find out what drugs you are using
right
Hello Nally
What should I do if your uniform will get dirty if you do this?
It doesn't matter
Just wash it
You admit it so readily
It seems that there is no need to check
How to post on social media
To increase the click-through rate
Please help me think of a title
Aren't you an expert in this field?
Jay
Who told you to be so ignorant?
Feel free to touch my people
So you obviously know everything
Just now you were testing me in the teacher's office
But seeing Na Li give in so quickly
Don't you feel happy?
Jay, are you really...
Seulgi
you shouldn't be angry with me
You should thank me
I'll help you deal with it neatly...
That scumbag who bullied you
That's not the point now, right?
Isn't it?
what is that
My dad's relic
and my profile
Why is it in your hands?
Liu Jieyi
answer me